{
    "id": "accbc93c0e01423fb634573635a4a0e7",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………………. a loud noise, the thief ran away.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Hearing",
                "Heard"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ……………….. fat to run fast.",
            "description": "Note the pattern too...to...",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. he left home early, he reached school late.",
            "description": "Although is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Although",
                "Because"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Vicky ……………….. was once my student is now an acclaimed writer.",
            "description": "That cannot be used to refer to people in non-identifying relative clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "who",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… being faster, the hare could not beat the tortoise in the race.",
            "description": "We use a preposition before an ing form. ",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Although",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… hard you may work, you cannot beat him.",
            "description": "However means the same as no matter how.",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "7……………………… his poor health, he still goes to work regularly.",
            "description": "Either despite or in spite of can be used here. ",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Although",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… you hurry up, you will miss the train.",
            "description": "Unless is similar to if not. ",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If",
                "In case"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The faster you run, ………………….. you get tired.",
            "description": "In this structure, the + comparative is used in both clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "sooner",
                "the sooner",
                "the more soon"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The apples ………………… I bought yesterday are very good.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The weather …………………. fine, we went for a walk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "being",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. he was suffering from fever, he could not attend the class.",
            "description": "As gives the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "As",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}